=Love Lurking=
=الحب الكامن=
=Episode 3=
=الحلقة 3=
Stop!
قف!
Let go!
اتركه!
Tell me.
أخبرني.
How did you know I wasn't here?
كيف عرفت أنني لست هنا؟
You admit it?
هل تعترف بذلك؟
You were testing me?
هل كنت تختبرني؟
How did you know?
كيف عرفت؟
Say it.
قلها.
The rain started after we came back.
بدأ المطر بعد عودتنا.
But there were muddy footprints in the bathroom.
ولكن كانت هناك آثار أقدام موحلة في الحمام.
So
لذا
you must have gone out.
لا بد أنك خرجت.
You're the "intruder" they want, right?
أنت "المتطفل" الذي يريدونه، أليس كذلك؟
How about we make a deal?
ماذا عن أن نعقد صفقة؟
If you let me go,
إذا سمحت لي بالذهاب،
I promise I won't tell anyone about it.
أعدك أنني لن أخبر أحداً بذلك.
You think since you know about that,
أنت تعتقد أنك تعرف ذلك،
you can threaten me?
هل يمكنك تهديدي؟
I can kill you right now.
أستطيع أن أقتلك الآن.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
Kill me.
اقتلني.
Are you really not afraid of death?
هل أنت حقا لا تخاف من الموت؟
I am.
أنا أكون.
I'm so afraid of death.
أنا خائفة جدًا من الموت.
So I'm trying to find a way to live, right?
لذا فأنا أحاول العثور على طريقة للعيش، أليس كذلك؟
If they can't find the intruder tonight,
إذا لم يتمكنوا من العثور على الدخيل الليلة،
they'll naturally suspect someone here.
من الطبيعي أن يشتبهوا في وجود شخص هنا.
If you kill me now,
إذا قتلتني الآن،
no one can testify for you.
لا أحد يستطيع أن يشهد لك.
I bet you'll end up like me.
أراهن أنك سوف تصبح مثلي في النهاية.
Either let me go,
إما أن تدعني أذهب،
or
أو
we die together.
نموت معا.
I really underestimated you.
لقد قللت من شأنك حقا.
But I hate being threatened.
لكنني أكره أن أتعرض للتهديد.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
What is this?
ما هذا؟
If I press this,
إذا ضغطت على هذا،
the thing on your ankle will explode immediately.
الشيء الموجود على كاحلك سوف ينفجر على الفور.
Forget about removing it.
انسى إزالته.
Because only I have the code.
لأنه أنا فقط من يملك الكود.
You're mad.
أنت مجنون.
Everyone here is mad.
الجميع هنا مجانين.
If you dare to say a word,
إذا تجرأت على قول كلمة،
you will surely die.
سوف تموت بالتأكيد.
Why do this to me?
لماذا تفعل بي هذا؟
I just want to go home.
أريد فقط أن أعود إلى المنزل.
Useless!
عديم الفائدة!
You mean
هل تقصد
the ledger was stolen?
هل تم سرقة الدفتر؟
If we can't find it,
إذا لم نتمكن من العثور عليه،
we will both die.
سوف نموت كلانا.
Kun, I swear.
كون، أقسم.
My security was airtight.
لقد كان أمني محكمًا.
Not even a fly could get in.
حتى الذبابة لم تتمكن من الدخول.
Then tell me,
ثم أخبرني
how did the intruder get in?
كيف دخل المتسلل؟
Could it be
هل يمكن أن يكون
that we have a mole here?
أن لدينا شامة هنا؟
K, open the door.
ك، افتح الباب.
Tonight, someone was indeed
في هذه الليلة، كان هناك شخص بالفعل
quite suspicious.
مشبوهة تماما.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
(No, I can't confront him directly now.)
(لا، لا أستطيع مواجهته بشكل مباشر الآن.)
I want to take a shower.
أريد أن أستحم.
Everyone here is mad.
الجميع هنا مجانين.
If you dare to say a word,
إذا تجرأت على قول كلمة،
you will surely die.
سوف تموت بالتأكيد.
(Keeping her will eventually be a problem.)
(الاحتفاظ بها سوف يصبح مشكلة في نهاية المطاف.)
(Even though he doesn't kill me now,)
(حتى لو لم يقتلني الآن)
(there's no guarantee later he will...)
(لا يوجد ضمان أنه سوف يفعل ذلك لاحقًا...)
Why took so long?
لماذا استغرق الأمر وقتا طويلا؟
Well...
حسنًا...
Can you give me some other clothes?
هل يمكنك أن تعطيني بعض الملابس الأخرى؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Stop.
قف.
I'll have someone bring you some clothes later.
سأطلب من شخص ما أن يحضر لك بعض الملابس لاحقًا.
K.
ك.
Kun wants to see you.
كون يريد رؤيتك.
Got it.
فهمتها.
I warn you.
أحذرك.
Stay in this room.
ابقى في هذه الغرفة.
Or face the consequences.
أو مواجهة العواقب.
(There are so many guards outside.)
(هناك الكثير من الحراس بالخارج.)
(There's no way to escape.)
(لا يوجد وسيلة للهروب.)
Take her.
خذها.
Kun,
متى،
why don't we interrogate K directly?
لماذا لا نستجوب K بشكل مباشر؟
You think I don't want to?
هل تعتقد أنني لا أريد ذلك؟
If we do anything to him
إذا فعلنا له أي شيء
but find out nothing,
ولكن لم أجد شيئا،
the boss will be unhappy.
سيكون الرئيس غير سعيد.
But this woman
ولكن هذه المرأة
can let me know a lot of things.
أستطيع أن أعلمني الكثير من الأشياء.
Kun, you're so wise.
كون، أنت حكيم جدًا.
You don't think
أنت لا تعتقد
K will come to save you, do you?
هل سيأتي K لإنقاذك؟
I am his person now.
أنا شخصه الآن.
Aren't you afraid
ألا تخاف؟
that he'll come after you?
أنه سيأتي بعدك؟
K
ك
would offend me for a mere plaything?
هل سيؤذيني مجرد لعبة؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Did K leave the room last night?
هل غادر K الغرفة الليلة الماضية؟
(I can't tell him.)
(لا أستطيع أن أخبره).
(If I do, I'll die immediately.)
(إذا فعلت ذلك، سأموت على الفور.)
No.
لا.
I knew you wouldn't talk so easily.
كنت أعلم أنك لن تتحدث بسهولة.
So
لذا
I've prepared something nice for you
لقد أعددت لك شيئا لطيفا
to "entertain" you well.
"لتسلية"ك بشكل جيد.
This is something worse than death.
هذا شيء أسوأ من الموت.
Wait.
انتظر.
What?
ماذا؟
You'll talk now?
هل ستتحدث الآن؟
We...
نحن...
We didn't leave the room.
لم نغادر الغرفة.
Are you fooling me?
هل انت تخدعني؟
But I can help you.
ولكن بإمكاني مساعدتك.
What?
ماذا؟
I can monitor him for you.
أستطيع مراقبته لك.
With just you?
معك فقط؟
With just me.
معي فقط.
He took me here.
لقد أخذني إلى هنا.
He won't guard against me.
لن يحرسني.
Gu Nian,
قو نيان,
why should I trust you?
لماذا يجب أن أثق بك؟
Because
لأن
I want to live.
أريد أن أعيش.
You want to live?
هل تريد أن تعيش؟
Alright.
على ما يرام.
As long as you say
طالما تقول
K left the room last night,
غادر ك الغرفة الليلة الماضية،
I'll let you go immediately.
سأدعك تذهب على الفور.
But if you don't say it,
ولكن إذا لم تقل ذلك،
I will show
سوف اظهر
no mercy.
لا رحمة.
You have three seconds.
لديك ثلاث ثواني.
One.
واحد.
Two.
اثنين.
He...
هو...
♪What is secretly stirring♪
♪ما الذي يتحرك سرا♪
K,
ك,
you're quite something.
أنت شيء مميز.
Rampaging on my turf over a woman?
الهياج في بلدي بسبب امرأة؟
I'm here to tell you,
أنا هنا لأخبرك،
she's yours to do as you wish.
إنها ملكك لتفعل بها ما تشاء.
♪Waving hands to break free from the splendid cage♪
♪تلويح الأيدي للتحرر من القفص الرائع♪
But if you want to use her against me,
ولكن إذا كنت تريد استخدامها ضدي،
I won't let you go.
لن أدعك تذهب.
I didn't mean that.
لم أقصثد ذلك
Now everyone must be screened.
الآن يجب على الجميع أن يخضعوا للفحص.
Do you think
هل تعتقد
she could sneak past your guards to steal?
هل يمكنها التسلل أمام حراسك لسرقة؟
I didn't tell you
لم أخبرك
that someone stole something last night.
أن أحدهم سرق شيئًا الليلة الماضية.
Do you think you can hide it from me?
هل تعتقد أنك تستطيع إخفاء ذلك عني؟
Once I finish interrogating her,
بمجرد أن أنتهي من استجوابها،
I'll know who the mole is.
سأعرف من هو الخلد.
♪There are two endings, whether you understand or not♪
♪هناك نهايتان، سواء فهمت أم لا♪
K,
ك,
are you trying to rebel?
هل تحاول التمرد؟
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪
Are you seeking death?
هل تبحث عن الموت؟
Are you trying to rebel?
هل تحاول التمرد؟
Kun,
متى،
are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
How are you? Can you still walk?
كيف حالك؟ هل مازلت تستطيع المشي؟
I will take her away now.
سوف آخذها بعيدا الآن.
Let Boss come to me.
دع الرئيس يأتي إلي.
I've already given you chances.
لقد أعطيتك فرصًا بالفعل.
You don't want it.
أنت لا تريد ذلك.
Get him!
احصل عليه!
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪
♪Can't see who's instigating from behind♪
♪لا أستطيع أن أرى من يحرض من الخلف♪
♪Life is the same for all, and now the world calls♪
♪الحياة هي نفسها للجميع، والآن العالم ينادي♪
♪The future is here, but I'm true to my first dreams♪
♪المستقبل هنا، ولكنني مخلص لأحلامي الأولى♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪
♪Cannot see who is pulling the strings behind♪
♪لا أستطيع أن أرى من يسحب الخيوط من الخلف♪
♪The wound still aches, and the memory is not yet over♪
♪الجرح لا يزال يؤلمني، والذكرى لم تنته بعد♪
♪There are two endings, whether you understand or not♪
♪هناك نهايتان، سواء فهمت أم لا♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪
♪Cannot see who is pulling the strings behind♪
♪لا أستطيع أن أرى من يسحب الخيوط من الخلف♪
♪The wound still aches, and the memory is not yet over♪
♪الجرح لا يزال يؤلمني، والذكرى لم تنته بعد♪
♪There are two endings, whether you understand or not♪
♪هناك نهايتان، سواء فهمت أم لا♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪
♪Cannot see who is tracking from behind♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية من يتتبعني من الخلف♪
♪The heart still beats, total blood-red before my eyes♪
♪لا يزال القلب ينبض، أحمر اللون كالدم أمام عيني♪
♪Only one ending remains, whether it helps or not♪
♪تبقى نهاية واحدة فقط، سواء كانت مفيدة أم لا♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪
♪Cannot see who is tracking from behind♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية من يتتبعني من الخلف♪
♪The heart still beats, total blood-red before my eyes♪
♪لا يزال القلب ينبض، أحمر اللون كالدم أمام عيني♪
♪Only one ending remains, whether it helps or not♪
♪تبقى نهاية واحدة فقط، سواء كانت مفيدة أم لا♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪